Aleena Fatima Khalid

Content Writer | Software Engineering Student

Contact

ainookhalid@gmail.com http://linkedin.com/in/aleenakhalid14 https://www.instagram.com/loveatthecoffeeshop/

Education

BSc in Software Engineering (2020-2024), FAST NUCES, Islamabad

- Dean's List holder.
- Have taken multiple courses to enhance English writing skills, including English Composition and Comprehension and, Technical and Business Writing.

Summary

Enthusiastic student, eager to contribute to the field through hard work, attention to detail and excellent comprehension skills. Enhancing studies and learning along with the love of writing. Experienced writer of 5+ years composing short stories, fiction pieces, articles, poetry, novellas and other short prose.

Experience

Content writer • Quran and Sunnah society (Fast, Islamabad) • October 2022 – present

- Produce content involving the Quran and Sunnah.
- Collaborate and develop content with a team of 5+ writers.

Content head • women in tech – GDSC (Fast, Islamabad) • September 2022 – present

- Produce content involving women empowerment and women in tech.
- Lead a team of 5+ writers, and collaborate with them.
- Develop content strategies.

Freelance writer • Instagram • July 2021 – present

- Produce content pieces on a range of niches including product descriptions, reviews, website copy, interview questionnaires, guided articles etc.
- Keep track of SEO strategies.
- Enhance content with creative problem solving, and efficient research.

Co-founder• Chai Kahani • May 2020 – present

- Co-founded a spoken word poetry platform, with a writer friend.
- Curated an extremely talented circle of poets, writers, and artists, who perform on 'Chai Kahani'.
- Currently working on 'Chai Kahani' writing workshops and bundles.

Creative art blogger • Instagram • July 2018 – present

- Presented a creative approach to the global perspectives.
- Wrote short stories, poetry, articles, and blogs.
- Published a zine "Qurencia" with a close group of other writers.
- Currently working on a novel.

Content writer • Meraki Magazine • July 2018 – July 2019
Produced articles and fiction pieces according to provided themes.